Privacy

What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you place an order or fill out the contact form. When contacting us, you may be asked to enter your name and e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

* To contact you for support, warranty or product related queries
* To improve our website

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order such as shipping information.

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

We do not store any of your private information (e.g. credit cards, etc.) on any of our servers.

Do we use cookies?

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user.

Our website does not use cookies of any sort.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.

We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

Terms & Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website [there](https://www.nimbusaudio.ch/assets/nimbus-cgv-2017.09.pdf).

Your consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on 4-Sep-2017.

Contacting us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, please contact us at:

info (at) nimbusaudio.ch

 Copyright ©2022 Nimbus Electronics Sàrl | [Terms and conditions](https://www.nimbusaudio.ch/assets/nimbus-cgv-2017.09.pdf) | [Privacy](https://www.nimbusaudio.ch/privacy.html)
